RUI SERÔDIO MELO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Madrid

ruimsmelo@gmail.com

+351 91 737 86 31



After 5 years as a commercial diver in one of the world's best aquarium I decided to career change to web developer and move to Madrid.

With my engineering background and Ironhack's bootcamp along with all the personal projects I keep working on to fuel my learning I feel ready to enter the tech industry workplace.

I'm most skilled with the MERN stack but I have been learning ThreeJS and Figma as of late.

FULL STACK

#REACT

#WEB DESIGN

WORK EXPERIENCE

2023

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

NerveCenter - Start Up
Internship

2022 - 2023

COMMERCIAL DIVER

Promergulho – Lisbon Oceanarium

Diving Team Leader

2018 - 2022

COMMERCIAL DIVER

Promergulho - Lisbon Oceanarium Diving Team

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

Spanish

SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- MongoDB
- Node.JS
- Express.JS
- JWT
- Git
- C
- AutoCAD
- Figma

EDUCATION

Ironhack

2023 Full Stack Web Development

Casco Antiguo Diving Center

2018 Commercial Diving

Faculdade de Ciências da Univ. Lisboa

2015-2017 Computer Engineering - Unfinished

Faculdade de Ciências da Univ. Lisboa

2012-2015 Environmental Engineering - Unfinished